{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "he is Personal pronoun", "question": "Select appropiate Personal pronoun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that _____________ lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["He", "I", "he", "they"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to _____________ him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["use", "take", "go", "do"]}, {"explanation": "him is Personal pronoun", "question": "Select appropiate Personal pronoun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let _____________ go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["I", "He", "they", "him"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "that", "a", "went"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the _____________ , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["crew", "plane", "lion", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him _____________ he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["for", "of", "that", "by"]}, {"explanation": "go is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["help", "do", "go", "take"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The _____________ was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["cook", "number", "manan", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search _____________ a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["of", "into", "that", "for"]}, {"explanation": "few is Adjective", "question": "Select appropiate Adjective from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a _____________ hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["new", "long", "few", "pro"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went _____________ search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["in", "that", "from", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: hunters", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["the", "a", "lion", "hunters"]}, {"explanation": "the is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured _____________ lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["some", "a", "this", "the"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["take", "the", "in", "to"]}], "success": 1}